ioerror.us 2005-12-20

# Privacy Policy - Homeland Security or Homeland Stupidity

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site.

Here’s the summary: We sometimes collect personal information, but we never use it for purposes of sending you marketing. You won’t receive any spam if you leave your email address here.

### What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

### Personal Information You Choose to Provide

You may browse our Web site without providing any personal information. However, in order to post to our Web site, we require certain personal information, such as your name and email address.

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

### Web Site Use Information

Similar to other Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small pieces of code called “web beacons” or “clear gifs” to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them.

### How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our Web site. We do not use it for marketing purposes.

### What Are Cookies?

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

### How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?

Cookies are used to store your Web site preferences. Cookies which cannot be used to specifically identify you are used for site analysis, such as determining which sections of the web site are most popular or in need of improvement. We may use a third party to serve cookies for site analysis.

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

We do not share your personal information with any third parties, unless required by valid governmental authority, such as a court order.

### Public Forums

If you choose to participate in public forums, comments, or other similar activity on our Web site, the name and Web site address you provide, along with your comments, will be made available to the general public. You can choose what name, Web site and comment to provide to the general public. You retain the copyright to your comments and grant us a non-exclusive, royalty-free, worldwide license to redistribute your comments on the page on which you post them. While we require your email address, we do not provide it to the general public. We reserve the right to remove any posting which is illegal under U.S. law, or which contains copyrighted materials for which you do not have permission to republish.

### Contact Us

You may correspond with us by emailing us at [error@ioerror.us](mailto:error%40ioerror.us).

Notices under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, as well as any other legal correspondence, should be sent to:

Michael Hampton  
308 E Burlington St  
#250  
Iowa City, IA 52240  
USA
